All right. Lab culture.
Death and destruction. I can just film it all
the time. Okay.
So. Don't film me. All right.
My personal opinion on it,
I'm very much leaning into, I should
be
there, so much as we can afford it as it's like
an affordable resource for us to use because
it is expensive.
I think using it as viewing it as a lab assistant
and a TA, kind of as Sam mentioned,
are my two favorite things for it, because I
think in that way, if it's a lab assistant, it's
doing things that you know how to do,
or maybe it's taught you how to do,
and it's just taking away some of the grunt work,
and maybe it can provide some suggestions or
other things, but, like, ultimately, you're leading
everything, you're designing the experiment,
you're being the architect or manager behind
it. Yeah.
And avoiding. using it as a crutch.
Basically, I'm just stating what I put in my
comment. Yeah.
I agree.
You know, it's a tool to be used, you know,
like it says in the scriptures, we are,
you know, we're supposed to be things that act
and not to be acted upon.
So if AI, if we start using AI too much, then
start, then AI starts using us.
And that should be the other way around.
And like I said earlier,
you know, it's just like Tony Stark and Jarvis.
You know, Jarvis takes away some of the grunt
work, you know, Jarvis does some of the little
things. It does, you know, the quick, like, AI
test or quick analysis of something.
But Tony Stark knows all this stuff.
He's the one that's like, hey,
I know this real
quick, you know, analyze this for two seconds
because he already knows all the stuff.
He knows what all the words mean.
He knows how to do it.
It just needs a quick, easy thing.
But, you know,
if we're not learning anything in the process,
the whole point of research is to learn, you
know, the whole point of research is to learn,
to build the skills that we need.
And if AI is doing it all for us, then we won't
ever gain those skills. And we need to be the
ones gaining the skills and using AI to
support us.
Because AI is not our equal.
No. It is our tool. Yeah,
that's a very useful tool.
I think. what you put forth is really good.
I think it would be a good habit for each of
us in the lab that a good practice that if at
any time it feels like the work we're doing isn't
our own or it feels like we're being told
what next step to do by the
AI and not a professor ourselves that we just
immediately stop and just do like a self -evaluation
of like, okay, how am I using AI in this way?
Is it telling me what to do or am I telling it
what to do? know, is it acting upon me or am
I acting upon it? Because that is a really good
scriptural example for it.
But I think it would be a good practice to, like,
kind of have that mental check.
Because I've had both in my lab work.
There's been times where I'm like, okay,
I am telling it to do this, asking it to do that,
and it's doing this. And those other times when
I'm like, oh, hey,
oh, it thinks I should do this next.
Okay, that would be a good idea.
And so it ranges. But I think having that mental
evaluation, like,
being metacognit of, like,
when it's acting upon us or not, it would be
a really good practice for us.
For sure. Being aware, not just mindlessly, like,
do this.
Because this is a little pretty slope.
I mean, it's really easy to just start, like,
maybe you start in control and slowly, like,
you go out of controls, you do it.
And you don't even realize it,
because it can slowly start to just be
doing more. It's like flaxing cord.
The flaxing cord, which the devil wrap.
you actually really love that reference because
it took me a while to learn that flexing cord
is like really thin twasically it's not super
strong uh -huh it's only when you're wrapped
with it like a thousand times that it actually
like you can't break it you know so exactly
yeah anything else you want to add
nope